kqed.org 2019-12-10

# Privacy Policy | About KQED

This Privacy Policy, along with our [Terms of Service](http://ww2.kqed.org/about/terms-service/), applies to all users of KQED Inc.’s (“KQED”) digital platforms, including this website (the “Site”), embeddable content that we may make available for use on other people’s websites or digital platforms, and our apps (collectively, the “KQED Platform”), other than third party content, as discussed in Links to Third Party Sites and Services, below.

  * We only collect your personal information when you voluntarily provide it on the KQED Platform.
  * We will honor your browser’s Do Not Track setting.
  * We only use cookies on our website to collect aggregated website usage data and to improve our services and your user experience.
  * For more detailed information about our privacy practices, please read our complete privacy policy below.

### Our Commitment to Your Privacy

We take your privacy seriously and want you to understand how we do and don’t use information about you. Below you’ll find information about our commitment to ensuring the privacy of your personally identifiable information (such as your full name, address, email address, telephone number, and/or other identifying information) and preserving the integrity of the medium. If you have any questions or concerns, please send us an email at [faq@kqed.org](mailto:webmaster@kqed.org).

## How We Collect Information

### A. Information You Provide to Us Voluntarily

You may voluntarily give us information like:

  * Your login information;
  * Your email address (e.g. when you sign up for an email newsletter);
  * Your name and/or address (e.g. when you register for a contest or sweepstakes);
  * Your phone number (e.g. if you text us);
  * Donation / payment information;
  * Your Content submissions (e.g. in response to a call for nature photos for our Quest TV show)

### B. Information We Collect Automatically from Users

When you use the KQED Platform, we may automatically recognize certain information like your IP address, date of your visit, operating system, what type of device you are using, geo-targeting information (what geographic area you’re in), and your user behavior (e.g. how long you stay on a page, or amount of time spent listening to audio files).

  * **KQED Cookies**

KQED uses cookies, other similar small files sent to your computer which store information through your browser and web beacons (tiny graphics, aka “pixel tags”) as part of our digital functionality (e.g. to store your preferences or password and understand your user behavior), and to offer responsive elements based on users’ actions. This information helps us improve the experience you and other visitors have with the KQED Platform. For more information on cookies and how to delete them, go to: [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

  * **Third Party Cookies**

In addition, KQED uses third party vendors that provide services for the KQED Platform (e.g. analytics) which may each use their own cookies and web beacons as part of the KQED Platform. At no time do these cookies reveal your name, address, or e-mail address (even if you have entered these in specific areas of the Site).

## How We Use Information

### Personally Identifiable Information

KQED may ask for your personally identifiable information (like your name, address, email address, phone number or credit card information) but we will never willfully disclose any of this information to a non-affiliated third party without first receiving your permission (unless required by law). This means, e.g., we may email you to join a new newsletter list or ask you to renew your membership when it expires, and we may share your information with third party vendor service providers, but only for the purpose of helping us do these sorts of things and never for their own use . These third party service providers maintain customer databases with email addresses obtained via the KQED Platform and other collection methods (events, phone calls, etc.) and visitors who have provided them to us by registering at our site, signing up for a newsletter or email, emailing questions to us about the services, donors who submit online contributions or online buyers who make a purchase. These third party vendors are required to maintain the privacy of all such information in their possession or control and can only use the information on our behalf for the purpose that we have contracted them, for example sending you a newsletter. They are not authorized to use your information for any other purpose.

KQED may use your personally identifiable information only for conducting activities such as those stated above, or for internal marketing and promotional purposes, KQED Teach platform evaluation, and to improve the Platform experience through personalization features.

In the instance when certain personal information is required for a particular activity it will be explicitly stated and explained at the time of submission. If you do not want this information to be collected or used for these purposes, you can simply “opt-out” by choosing not to participate in the activity, such as a sweepstakes entry. Our visitors need to recognize, however, that under certain circumstances, if they select to “opt-out” they may not be eligible for certain activities for which the personally identifiable information is needed.

### Payment Information

When you provide us payment information in order to process a donation or purchase an item, this information is encrypted, using reasonable, industry-standard security measures, and is used (generally by our third party vendors) only to fulfill your transaction.

### Non Personally Identifiable Information

We use other information (other than personal information and payment information) for things like improving your user experience (e.g. your user history on our digital platforms may be used to provide recommendations to you and other users of the same device), selecting third-party vendors who best meet our needs, and notifying our users about our programs and events. In doing this, we do share non-personally identifying information and payment information with third parties.

Please note that if you share personal information through a public feature that it may become public (e.g. if you include your email address in a comment, other users will see it, or if you include your name in a content submission, it may be read on the air or posted online to attribute the content).

Lastly, if we are required by law to share your information (including personal and payment information), we will share to the extent necessary to comply with the request.

### List Sharing Policy

On occasion, we may make our membership list available to other, carefully selected, 501(c)(3) non-profit organizations. For more information regarding KQED’s policies on the handling and use of KQED’s membership list, please see [KQED’s Membership List Policy](http://www.kqed.org/support/membership/help/membership-list-policy.jsp).

### Do Not Track

If you enable the Do Not Track setting in your browser, we won’t record your visit to our website and the third party cookies on our pages will be disabled. [Find more information on Do Not Track](http://donottrack.us/)

### Links to Third Party Sites and Services

The KQED Platform contains links to services maintained by third parties that do not follow the same privacy practices as KQED. In some cases, we may also include certain embedded tools provided and controlled by third parties, or that permit you to submit information to these third parties. These services and tools are governed by the terms and policies of those third parties. The KQED Platform also includes widgets from third party services, e.g. a button that allows you to “like” an article on Facebook. Please review these services’ own privacy policies for more information.

### Children

Children should always get permission from their parents before sending any information about themselves (such as their names, email addresses, and phone numbers) via the web or mobile device, to KQED or to anyone else. The KQED services are not directed at children under the age of 13 and KQED does not knowingly allow anyone under the age of 13 to provide any personally-identifying information to KQED. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for any KQED Services or provide any information about yourself.

## Acceptance of This Policy

By using this site, you signify your agreement to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use the KQED Platform. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the KQED Platform following the posting of any changes to these terms shall mean that you have accepted those changes. If you have any questions or concerns, please email us at [faq@kqed.org](mailto:webmaster@kqed.org).

## Terms of Use

Please also make sure to read the [KQED Public Media Website’s Terms of Service](https://ww2.kqed.org/about/terms-service/) to understand the additional terms and conditions which apply to your use of the KQED Platform.

_Effective_ : May 5, 2016
